Finding aid for University Herbarium (University of Michigan) Records, 1744-1745, 1851-1981, and 2001-2014
Bentley Historical Library
- Bartlett, Harley Harris, 1744-1855; 1875-1959
  - Correspondence and Associated Materials, 1875-1959
    - M
      - Muller, Herman J., 1949-1961 (Box 13)
        (effects of radiation; see also)
      - Munck, C., 1945 (Box 13)
      - Munos-Pizarro, Carlos, 1944-1945 (Box 13)
        (Chile)
      - Munz, Philip A., 1924-1954 (Box 13)
        (Oenothera, U.S. Nat'l. Herb.)
      - Musher, Sidney, 1928 (Box 13)
        (vegetable oils)
      - Musselman, H.H., 1947 (Box 13)
      - Muzik, Thomas James, 1942-1956 (Box 13)
      - Myers, Ernest E., 1945 (Box 13)
      - Myers, William I., 1947 (Box 13)
    - N
      - Nainggolan, Marah Tigor, 1919-1927 (Box 13)
        (Kisaran)
      - Nainggolan, Moehammad Sjariff, Sinaksak (Box 13)
      - Nakashima, Tomosuke, 1929 (Box 13)
      - National Geographic, 1940 (Box 13)
        (palm article; see also Vosburgh, F.G.)
      - National Research Council, 1920-1950 (Box 13)
      - National Research Council-Div. Biology and Agriculture, 1956 (Box 13)
      - National Research Council-Fellowships, 1923-1948 (Box 13)
      - National Research Council-Pacific Science Board, 1947-1955 (Box 13)
      - National Research Council, Philippines, 1935-1937 (Box 13)
      - National Resources Planning Board, 1942 (Box 13)
        (roster of scientific personnel)
      - National Travel Club, 1935 (Box 13)
      - Natural Areas, 1945-1946 (Box 13)
        (Pine Knob, Eberwhite Woods)
      - Navarrete, Jesus P., 1941 (Box 13)
      - Necker, Walter L., 1945 (Box 13)
      - Nell T.G., 1956 (Box 13)
      - Nelson, Aven, 1922-1936 (Box 13)
      - Nelson, D.H. (Box 13)
        (see Nat'l. Res. Council -- Fellowships)
      - Nelson, Noland F., 1945 (Box 13)
      - Nemenzo, Francisco, 1937-1947 (Box 13)
      - Newcombe, Curtis L., 1945 (Box 13)
        (conservation-Jackson Hole)
      - Newcombe, Frederick C., 1920-1928 (Box 13)
      - Newcomer, Wilbur S., 1945 (Box 13)
      - New England Botanical Club, 1905-1944 (Box 13)
      - New England Historic Genealogical Society, 1938 (Box 13)
        (Roger Williams 1 letter from H.C.Darrell, editor)
      - New York Academy of Sciences, 1941-1949 (Box 13)
      - Nichols, George Elwood, 1920-1939 (Box 13)
      - Nieuwland, Julius A., 1923-1927 (Box 13)
        (re E.L. Greene papers)
      - Noamesi, Gottlieb K., 1957 (Box 13)
      - Noe, A.C., 1923 (Box 13)
        (courses in paleobotany)
      - Noll, Carmen (Mrs. Jerry), 1947 (Box 13)
        (personal-student?, A.A.)
      - Norem, Winfred Luther, 1932 (Box 13)
      - Norris, Porter, 1944 (Box 13)
        (lost baggage Pan Am Airways)
      - Northern Nut Growers' Association, 1928 (Box 13)
        (letters from H.D.Spencer and W.G.Bixby)
      - Nowell, R.I., 1937 (Box 13)
        (Battle Creek Arboretum Project)
      - Nye, P.H., 1958 (Box 13)
      - Nyhus, Paul 0., 1942-1944 (Box 13)
        (Argentina; guayule see Short, Ena D.)
      - Nyland, D., 1920 (Box 13)
      - Nyland, W.A., 1945 (Box 13)
        (organic gardening)
    - O
      - Oak Ridge National Laboratory, 1948-1949 (Box 13)
        (irradiation of seeds)
      - Oberwetter, P.H., 1910 (Box 13)
      - O'Brien, James G. (Box 13)
        (see Nat'l. Resources Planning Board)
      - O'Conner, Esther, 1955 (Box 13)
      - Odegaard, Charles E., 1955 (Box 13)
        (director for Gardens)
      - Oehlkers, Freidrich, 1939 (Box 13)
      - Ogawa, N., 1936 (Box 13)
      - Ogden, Eugene C., 1945-1951 (Box 13)
      - Ohio State University Bulletin, 1948 (Box 13)
      - O'Keefe, G.W. (Box 13)
        (see U.S. Treasury Dept.-Customs)
      - Okkelberg, Peter, 1922-1946 (Box 13)
        (see also White, Stephen S., & War-related-CATS)
      - O'Neill, Hugh T., 1932-1949 (Box 13)
        (includes determinations)
      - Onodera, Isenosuke, 1928 (Box 13)
        (thanks)
      - O'Rourke, Mary, 1948 (Box 13)
      - Ortega, Maria L., 1937 (Box 14)
        (herbarium collection)
      - Orton, Clayton R., 1938 (Box 14)
      - Osborn, Chase S., 1929-1941 (Box 14)
      - Osgood, Albert J., 1934 (Box 14)
        (bronze masks)
      - Osmena, Sergio (Box 14)
        (see Philippines-J.R.H.Mem.Lib.)
      - Osterhout, George E., 1910 (Box 14)
      - Otis, Charles H., 1921-1944 (Box 14)
      - Ott, H.N., 1940; 1890s (Box 14)
        (botany at Mich. in)
      - Overbeck, H., 1937 (Box 14)
      - Over-population (Box 14)
        (see Wright, Quincy)
      - Owens, Clarence, 1945 (Box 14)
      - Ownbey, Gerald B., 1940 (Box 14)
        (re application)
    - P
      - Pablo, Felipa E., 1947 (Box 14)
        (application-Philippines)
      - Pablo, Manuel E., 1946 (Box 14)
        (Philippines-Manila Tribune)
      - Pablo, Winifred O'Connor, 1936 (Box 14)
      - Pacific Science Association-Council, 1951 (Box 14)
        (Pacific Science Bulletin)
      - Pacific Science Board (Box 14)
      - Pacific War Memorial, 1946-1949 (Box 14)
      - Pagan, Sutla M., 1947 (Box 14)
        (herbarium of Francis M. Pagan)
      - Paine, Frances R., 1951 (Box 14)
        (re Walter Van Fleet)
      - De Paiva Nello, Jos; Elias, 1956 (Box 14)
      - Pallis, Marietta, 1939 (Box 14)
        (re ecological paper)
      - Palmer, Marguerite, 1947 (Box 14)
        (staffing U. of Philippines)
      - Palmer, Walter G., 1945 (Box 14)
      - Palo, Macario A. (Box 14)
      - Panagra Club, 1945 (Box 14)
      - Pan American Society of Tropical Research, 1937 (Box 14)
      - Panganiban, Jose, 1941 (Box 14)
        (Philippines-stamps, rare book)
      - Panlilio, Filadelfo, 1947-1950 (Box 14)
        (Philippines; see also Gamboa, M.J.; Guggenheim Foundation)
      - Pardon, E.C., 1928-1948 (Box 14)
        ("buildings & grounds"; see also Bot. Gard.-Admin. & Smith, Shirley W.)
      - Parish, S.B., 1910 (Box 14)
      - Park, Man-Kyu, 1948 (Box 14)
        (Korean plant specimens)
      - Park, Stephen A., 1944 (Box 14)
        (CATS-Matuda)
      - Parker, DeWitt H., 1949 (Box 14)
        (biographical sketch)
      - Parker, Dorothy I., 1932-1936 (Box 14)
      - Parks, Thayne C., 1951 (Box 14)
        (Aleutians-appointment)
      - Parry, M.S., 1956 (Box 14)
      - Parsons, James J., 1955-1959 (Box 14)
      - Pascasio, Juan F., 1932 (Box 14)
        (Philippines-application)
      - Paterson, Richard, 1945 (Box 14)
        (A.S. collecting)
      - Patino, Lorenzo R., 1956 (Box 14)
      - Patterson, Gordon K., 1945 (Box 14)
      - Pavetti-Morin, Claudio V., 1945-1947 (Box 14)
        (Paraguay-student-travel-relations with State Dept.)
      - Pearce, J.E., 1934-1936 (Box 14)
        (anthropology)
      - Pearl, Raymond, 1915; 1928 (Box 14)
        (plant breeding; Botanical Abstracts)
      - Pearson, Larry W., 1947 (Box 14)
      - Pearson, T. Gilbert, 1942 (Box 14)
        (Int'l. Comm. for Bird Preservation)
      - Pease, Arthur Stanley., 1910-1929 (Box 14)
      - Peck, Mordant E., 1936 (Box 14)
        (temperature on dormancy)
      - Peck, Morton E., 1932 (Box 14)
        (collections in British Honduras)
      - Peckham, Howard H. (Box 14)
        (see Mrs. R.A. Hunt)
      - Peggy, 1926 (Box 14)
        (personal-cousin, California)
      - Pelley, Marion S., 1938 (Box 14)
      - Pelzer, Karl J., 1955-1956 (Box 14)
      - Pendleton, Robert L., 1947; 1957 (Box 14)
        (Comm. on Philippines; Fire & Prim.)
      - Pennell, Francis W., 1936-1952 (Box 14)
        (Scrophulariaceae; Nat'l. Herb.)
      - Peren, G.S., 1957 (Box 14)
      - Perkins, George M., 1945 (Box 14)
      - Perkins, J.A., 1949-1950 (Box 14)
      - Perry, Pennie E., 1946 (Box 14)
      - Petrick, A.W., 1923 (Box 14)
        (collection-plants)
      - Petry, Loren C., 1929 (Box 14)
        (fossil collection)
      - Phi Kappa Phi, 1935-1942 (Box 14)
        (Scholastic Honor Society)
      - Philadelphia Botanical Club, 1935 (Box 14)
        ("Bartonia")
      - Philatelic Advisor, 1955 (Box 14)
        (Ryukyan Islands; sweet potato)
      - Philately, 1945-1953 (Box 14)
        (see also Special Interests-Philately)
      - Philippine Foundation of America, 1946 (Box 14)
        (report of R.H.Barrett to J.W.Jones)
      - Philippines, 1941-1958 (Box 14)
      - Philippines Dept. Agriculture & Commerce-BPI, 1939 (Box 14)
        (Litoko)
      - Philippines-University: Bartlett-Santos Exchange, 1934 (Box 14)
      - Philippines-University: College of Agriculture, 1952 (Box 14)
        (data concerning)
      - Philippines-University: Staffing, 1947 (Box 14)
      - Philippines-Joseph Ralston Hayden Memorial Library, 1945-1948 (Box 14)
      - Philippines-National Teacher's College, 1939 (Box 14)
      - Philippines-News Digest, newspaper articles, 1946-1947 (Box 14)
      - Philippines-personal, 1946; 1950 (Box 14)
      - Phillips, Edwin A., 1938-1949 (Box 14)
        (student; Port Radium report on "Ecological Relationships)
      - Phillips, Howard M. (Box 14)
        (see Nat'l. Res. Council-Div. Biol. & Agr.)
      - Phillips, J.F.V., 1955-1956 (Box 14)
      - Phillips, L.H., 1937-1945 (Box 14)
        (Philippines, rotenone, Cinchona, rubber, philately)
      - Phillips, Walter S., 1959 (Box 14)
      - Philo, L.C., 1948 (Box 14)
      - "Phytopathology", 1948 (Box 14)
        (submitting paper)
      - Picard, Marilyn, 1946 (Box 14)
      - Pierce, Francis S., 1945 (Box 14)
      - Pierpont, Wilbur K., 1951-1957 (Box 14)
        (space; Botanical Gardens)
      - Pieters, Adrian J. (Box 14)
        (see U.S.D.A. B.P.I. Forage Crop Investigations)
      - Pikelis, Ann, 1955 (Box 14)
      - Pitt, John, 1951 (Box 14)
        (palms-Gambia)
      - Pittman, R.S., 1956 (Box 14)
      - Pius, Sister, 1930 (Box 14)
      - Platt, Robert B., 1946 (Box 14)
      - Pleasant Lakes Club, 1926; 1958 (Box 14)
      - Plimpton Press, 1927 (Box 14)
        (reprints)
      - Poleman, Horace I., 1942 (Box 14)
        (Batak manuscripts)
      - Polhamus, Loren G. (Box 14)
        (see H.S.D.A.-B.P.I.-Rubber Investigations)
      - Pollock, James B., 1921-1934 (Box 14)
        (Pisonia, department matters;)
      - Pollock, Nina, personal-A.A. (Box 14)
      - Polunin, Nicholas, 1955 (Box 14)
      - Pomerleau, Rene, 1946 (Box 14)
      - Pomeroy, 1945 (Box 14)
      - Poncet, Bishop A., 1958 (Box 14)
      - Pope, Merritt N. (Box 14)
        (see H.S.D.A. Agr. Res. Admin.)
      - Pope, Robert B., 1945 (Box 14)
      - Popenoe, Hugh, 1957 (Box 14)
      - Porsild, A. Erling, 1949-1951 (Box 14)
        (Great Bear Lake; see also Ammann, G.A.)
      - Porter, Cedric L., 1925-1953 (Box 14)
      - Porter, Charles H., 1954 (Box 14)
      - Porter, Harold L., 1945 (Box 14)
      - Porteres, Ro, 1957-1958 (Box 14)
      - Posey, Rollin B. (Box 14)
      - Postal Administration, United Nations, philately (Box 14)
      - Potter, ("Grandma"), 1907-1913 (Box 14)
      - Potter, Grace, 1936; 1943 (Box 14)
        (personal-cousin)
      - Potter, Laura, 1907-1917 (Box 14)
      - Potter, Merritt, 1912-1919 (Box 14)
        (personal-uncle)
      - Potzger, John E., 1944 (Box 14)
        (Friesner anniversary, "Floras of the Pacific")
      - Povah, Alfred H., 1917-1957 (Box 14)
        (see also Capelan Exped. (plant specimen))
      - Power, Eugene B., 1939 (Box 14)
      - Praeger, William E., 1929-1934 (Box 14)
      - Prager, E., 1909 (Box 14)
      - Pratt, Arnold E., 1933 (Box 14)
        (catalytic hydrogenation of sugars)
      - Prescott, Gerald W., 1934-1948 (Box 14)
      - Prescott, K.W., 1945 (Box 14)
      - Preston, D.A., 1940 (Box 14)
      - Preston, John F., 1945 (Box 14)
      - Price, Hazen, 1945 (Box 14)
      - Price, W. Armstrong, 1951 (Box 14)
        (Tamaulipas)
      - Prizer, Levis, 1911-1923 (Box 14)
      - Property-1601 Brooklyn Ave., A.A., personal (Box 14)
      - Property-1334 Newton St., N.E., Wash., D.C. personal (Box 14)
      - Prouty, Harvey, 1931 (Box 14)
        (plant & seed supplies-Wasatch)
      - Puckett, C.A. (Box 14)
      - Purkayastha, C.S., 1956 (Box 14)
      - Pyke, James, 1951 (Box 14)
      - Pyle, Robert, 1937 (Box 14)
        (Arboretums & Botanical Gardens; United Horticulture for the U.S.)
    - Q
      - Quate, Graham S. (Box 14)
        (see U.S.D.A. For. Agr. Service)
      - Quinn, Arthur Hobson, 1947 (Box 14)
      - Quinn, John D., A.F. collecting (Box 14)
      - Quirk, John, 1956 (Box 14)
      - Quisumbing, Delicia (Box 14)
        (see Quisumbing, Eduardo)
      - Quisumbing, Eduardo, 1936-1955 (Box 14)
        (Philippines, see also Uichanco, L.B.)
    - R
      - Radiation & Plant Heredity (Box 14)
        (see U.S. Office of Naval Research)
      - Radiation Research Society, 1951 (Box 14)
        (constitution and invitation to join)
      - Rahmat (Box 14)
        (see also Pyke, James; Hamel, C.; Bougham, W.; photograph)
      - Rainey, Froelich G., 1947 (Box 14)
        (staffing, U.Philippines)
      - Ramaley, Francis, 1933 (Box 14)
        ("Nomenclature of Plant Associations")
      - Ramirez, Orencio, 1936-1938 (Box 14)
      - Ramsdell, W.F. (Box 14)
      - Rand, Frederick V., 1920 (Box 14)
      - Rands, Robert D., 1923-1943 (Box 14)
      - Rankama, Kalervo, 1952 (Box 14)
        (reprint requests)
      - Rankin, William R., 1950-1951 (Box 14)
      - Rantaniemi, P.A., 1951 (Box 14)
        (testosterone)
      - Rappaport, J., 1947 (Box 14)
      - Rasmus, R.N., 1945 (Box 14)
      - Rateaver, Bargyla, 1936-1951 (Box 14)
        (student; see also Wagnon, Keith; Swingle, Charles F.)
      - Raup, Hugh M., 1948-1949 (Box 14)
        (Great Bear project; Ted Bank)
      - Raymond, G.J., 1955 (Box 14)
      - Razi, B.A., 1951 (Box 14)
      - Read, Bernard E., 1948 (Box 14)
        (Chinese Bot. literature)
      - Reading, Douglas, 1944 (Box 14)
      - Reardon, John J., 1949 (Box 14)
        (freshwater biology, Pacific Receipts, miscellaneous)
      - Recke, S. v.d., 1955 (Box 14)
      - Record, Samuel J., 1941 (Box 14)
        (mahogany)
      - Reddick, Donald, 1917-1919 (Box 14)
        (Botanical Abstracts; Journ. Agricultural Res.)
      - Reed, Charles S. II (Box 14)
      - Reed, Ernest, 1921t, 1941 (Box 14)
      - Reed, Howard S., 1949 (Box 14)
      - Rehder, Alfred, 1933-1937 (Box 14)
        (herbarium exchange)
      - Reid, A. McIntosh, 1929 (Box 14)
        (shales)
      - Reid, Charles F., 1939-1945 (Box 14)
        (Bibliography of the Amer. Possessions)
      - Reid, Fred M., 1910 (Box 14)
      - Reighard, Jacob, 1925 (Box 14)
      - Reischer, Helen S. (Box 14)
        (see Simpson, Helen F.)
      - Reissig, Jos; Luis, 1948 (Box 14)
      - Reitsma, Jenny, 1946 (Box 14)
      - Rendle, Alfred B., 1909 (Box 14)
        (British Museum)
      - Renner, O., 1922-1927 (Box 14)
      - Rentsch, Samuel B., A.F. collecting (Box 14)
      - Reprints, H.H.B., re disposal of (Box 14)
      - Research Club, University of Michigan, 1921-1946 (Box 14)
      - Retherford, K.L., 1942 (Box 14)
        (Mexican plants)
      - Reynolds, Carol (Box 14)
        (personal-daughter of Lena)
      - Reynolds, Ernest S., 1909-1938 (Box 14)
      - Reynolds, George, 1947 (Box 14)
        (staffing-U.Philippines)
      - Reynolds, Lena (Mrs. Vinton), personal -- cousin (Box 14)
      - Rhoades, Marcus M., 1943 (Box 15)
        ("Genetics")
      - Rhoades, Verne, 1954 (Box 15)
      - Rhode Island Ins. Co. (Brooks Newton), house insurance (Box 15)
      - Rhodesia-Natural Resources Bd., 1955-1956 (Box 15)
      - "Rhodora", 1924-1951 (Box 15)
      - Rice, Paul S., 1938 (Box 15)
        (directions for preparing specimens)
      - Rice, Warner G. (Box 15)
        (see Philippines-J.R.H. Mem. Library)
      - Richards, Charles D., 1946-1964 (Box 15)
      - Richards, Ruth R., 1940-1941 (Box 15)
      - Richardson, John (Box 15)
        (see Harvard Univ.)
      - Richardson, Robert C. (Box 15)
      - Rickett, Harold W., 1939-1949 (Box 15)
        (Bulletin, Torrey Botanical Club)
      - Riddle, Lincoln W., 1908 (Box 15)
        (lichens)
      - Riel, 1928 (Box 15)
      - Riepsamen, John F.C., 1934 (Box 15)
        (Batak (linguistics))
      - Rijks Ethnographisch Museum Leiden, 1931 (Box 15)
      - Riley, John C., 1945 (Box 15)
        (A. F. collecting)
      - Roe., Emeterio, 1950-1951 (Box 15)
        (Barbour scholars)
      - Robbins, Frank E., 1926-1952 (Box 15)
      - Robbins, William J., 1928-1959 (Box 15)
        (inc. description of collection on "languages of the Philippines" offered to Amer. Philosophical Soc.)
      - Roberts, Wilkie (Box 15)
      - Robertson, Betty M., 1938-1941 (Box 15)
      - Robertson, F.C.Ford, 1956 (Box 15)
      - Robertson, William B., 1954-1957 (Box 15)
      - Robinson, Benjamin L., 1926-1932 (Box 15)
      - Robyns, Walter, 1955-1956 (Box 15)
      - Rochanapurananda, Pue, 1958 (Box 15)
      - Rockefeller Foundation, 1924-1947 (Box 15)
        (see also Tsui, You-Wen)
      - Rodin, Robert J., 1945 (Box 15)
      - Rodriguez, Mario (Box 15)
        (see Expedition: Seven Seas)
      - Roeding, George C., 1924 (Box 15)
        (Juglans)
      - Rogers, Andrew D., III, 1941-1946 (Box 15)
        (Sullivant; Fernow)
      - Rogers, C. Marvin, 1945-1952 (Box 15)
      - Rogerson, Clark T., 1945 (Box 15)
      - Rojas Gil, William, 1956 (Box 15)
      - Philippines (Box 15)
      - Rollins, Reed C., 1935; 1951 (Box 15)
        (see also "Rhodora")
      - Romell, L.-G., 1956 (Box 15)
      - Rosahn, Paul D., 1947 (Box 15)
      - Rose, Joseph N., 1925 (Box 15)
        (cactus specimens)
      - Rosenberg, G.O. (?), photographic file (Box 15)
      - Roslund, Harry & Louise, 1945 (Box 15)
        (A.F. collecting in account of travel to and in India)
      - Roszel, Grace & James, 1948 (Box 15)
      - Roth, Fred G., 1936-1941 (Box 15)
      - Roth, Walter M., 1945-1949 (Box 15)
      - Rotor, Arturo B., 1945 (Box 15)
        (re Gavino Rotor)
      - Rousseau, Jacques, 1948 (Box 15)
        (Port Radium project)
      - Rowell, John B., 1952 (Box 15)
        (genetic diversity in radioactive)
      - Rowland, C.A., 1954 (Box 15)
      - Rowley, Jessie L., 1953 (Box 15)
        (Japanese Garden)
      - Roy, Kamala, 1936-1938 (Box 15)
        (re study at V of M)
      - Royal Oak Garden Club, 1935 (Box 15)
      - Rubber, 1944 (Box 15)
        (news clippings)
      - Rubber Investigation-Sumatra, 1917-1920 (Box 15)
        (38 items)
      - Ruedemann, Rudolph, 1929 (Box 15)
      - Rufus, W. Carl, 1932-1946 (Box 15)
        (History of Science; Barbour)
      - Ruggles, Byron P., 1910 (Box 15)
      - Ruiz, L.T., 1947 (Box 15)
        (Philippines-Silliman Univ.)
      - Runyon, Robert, 1930 (Box 15)
        (sabal palms)
      - Rusby, Henry H., 1936 (Box 15)
        (Rusby collections in U of M)
      - Rush, Frank, 1925 (Box 15)
        (seeds for Bot. Gard.-walnut, plums)
      - Russell, Carl P., 1932-1933 (Box 15)
        (Hist. of Scientific Work in)
      - Russell, Paul, 1931 (Box 15)
        (Prunus, see also U.S.D.A.-B.P.I.-foreign Seed & Plant Introduction)
      - Russell, William, 1948 (Box 15)
        (spelling reform)
      - "Ruth", 1931 (Box 15)
        (personal-cousin, Missouri)
      - Ruth, Albert, 1924-1934 (Box 15)
        (collections & books)
      - Ruthven, Alexander G., 1921-1945 (Box 15)
        (see also Exped. Carpelan)
      - Ryerson, Knowles A., 1929 (Box 15)
        (Inter-American Cooperation in Agricultural Education; Pacific Science Board, N.R.C.; see also Expedition: Carpelan)
    - S
      - Sackett, Mrs. R.W. (Alice), 1945 (Box 15)
        (vida)
      - Sadler, Robert C.W. (re), 1941 (Box 15)
      - Safford, Mrs. Homer E. (Gertrude S.), 1928 (Box 15)
        (lecture request, 1 letter from G.S.S.)
      - Safford, William E. (re), 1936 (Box 15)
        (Safford diaries)
      - Saha, J.C., 1945 (Box 15)
        (ergot)
      - Sahlins, Marshall D., 1956 (Box 15)
      - St. John, Edward P., 1951 (Box 15)
        (Ophioglossaceae)
      - St. John, Harold, 1932-1946 (Box 15)
      - St. John, Sister Mary, 1947 (Box 15)
        (A.F. collecting pamphlets)
      - Salgado, Eddie & Pacita, 1936-1951 (Box 15)
        (Philippine artist)
      - Salisbury, Edward, 1949; 1956 (Box 15)
        (Kew Gardens) re publications)
      - Salisbury, Laurence, 1946 (Box 15)
        (request for article for "Far)
      - Salvan, Paule, 1959 (Box 15)
      - Sambursky, Rubin, 1946 (Box 15)
        (request for help)
      - Samson, O.W., 1958 (Box 15)
      - Samuelsson, Gunnar (Box 15)
        (see Herbarium-Exch. & Loans-Sweden)
      - Sanders, Richard, 1946 (Box 15)
      - Sando, Charles E., 1919-1947 (Box 15)
        (see also Fischer, A.F.; positions; quinine, photographic file & Photograph Album)
      - Santos, Jose K., 1936-1950 (Box 15)
        (see also Ebalo, L.E.; Philippines Univ.: Bartlett-Santos Exch. & Ramirez, O.)
      - Santos, Jose Vera, 1936-1957 (Box 15)
        (Garnotia, Mexican grasslands; Honduras, Guatemala, Cinchona, financial support; suggestions for preparation of a local flora; Conzatti; photographs of specimens; Philippines Univ.; Philip-pine grasses)
      - Santos-Leal, Armando, 1955 (Box 15)
      - Sapper, Karl, 1936 (Box 15)
      - Sargeant, Howland H., 1944 (Box 15)
        (republication of foreign language)
      - Sargent, Chester (Box 15)
        (see U.S. Dept. of State-Fulbright Funds)
      - Sass, John E., 1925-1948 (Box 15)
        (student +)
      - Sasscer, E.R. (Box 15)
        (see U.S.D.A.-Bur. Entomol. & Pl.)
      - Saturen, I.M., 1945 (Box 15)
      - Sauer, Jonathan, 1955 (Box 15)
        (Herbarium accessions)
      - Savile, Douglas, 1939-1940 (Box 15)
      - Sawyer, Ralph A., 1946-1951 (Box 15)
        (research support)
      - Sax, Carl, 1939 (Box 15)
        (re J.G. O'Mara)
      - Sayles, John M., 1946 (Box 15)
      - Schaeffer, Bob, 1938 (Box 15)
      - Schaffner, John H., 1931 (Box 15)
        (equisetum)
      - Scharfer, A.E., 1954 (Box 15)
        (Cedar of Lebanon)
      - Scheips, Paul J., 1949 (Box 15)
      - Schenkman, Alfred, 1940 (Box 15)
      - Schepers, J.H.G., 1934 (Box 15)
        ("Sacred Edifices of the Batak...")
      - Schipp, William A., 1931 (Box 15)
      - Schipper, Arthur L., 1955 (Box 15)
        (Am. Midland Naturalist-Greene's "Landmarks")
      - de Schlippe, Pierre, 1957-1958 (Box 15)
      - Schloat, Don T., 1947 (Box 15)
        (staffing-Philippines)
      - Schmidt, Fern E., 1957 (Box 15)
      - Schmidt, Karl P., 1947-1948 (Box 15)
        (Chicago Nat. Hist. Mus.)
      - Schmidt, Waldo, 1945 (Box 15)
        (National Herbarium; Bikini exped.)
      - Schneider, Philip F., 1929 (Box 15)
      - Schnell, R., 1958 (Box 15)
      - Schnooberger, Irma, 1938 (Box 15)
      - Schopf, James M., 1936-1951 (Box 15)
      - Schorger, Mrs. A.W. (Margaret D.), 1928 (Box 15)
        (garden club lecture)
      - Schornherst, Ruth, 1931-1946 (Box 15)
      - Schramm, Jacob R., 1908-1953 (Box 15)
        (see also Bot. Soc. Amer. & Botanical Abstracts)
      - Schramm, Mildred W. (Box 15)
        (see Nat'l. Res. Council-Fellowship; Photograph Album)
      - Schrieke, B., 1934 (Box 15)
        ("Sacred Edifices....")
      - Schultes, Richard Evans, 1949 (Box 15)
      - Schulz, Ellen D., 1922 (Box 15)
        (plants for Bot. Garden)
      - Schuster, Rudolf M., 1951 (Box 15)
        (Aleutian Hepaticae)
      - Schwabe, G.H., 1946-1947 (Box 15)
      - Schweinfurth, Charles S., 1931-1945 (Box 15)
      - "Science", 1950-1952 (Box 15)
        (book reviews)
      - "Scientific Monthly", 1920; 1951 (Box 15)
        (publication, review)
      - Scoggan, Homer J., 1946-1952 (Box 15)
      - Scott, personal-A.A. (Box 15)
      - Scott, Byron N. (Box 15)
      - Scott, Dick, 1953 (Box 15)
        (walnuts)
      - Scott, H.O., 1910 (Box 15)
      - Scott, Irving D., 1928; 1937 (Box 15)